{
    "name": "Italian 1",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "apirte il libro"
            ],
            "answer": "Apirte il libro.",
            "failed": 21,
            "lastAsked": 1517253822.7354155,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Open the book.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 28
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "non voglio di",
                "non volgio",
                "non voglio"
            ],
            "answer": "non voglio...",
            "failed": 12,
            "lastAsked": 1517630285.5851858,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I don't want...\"?",
            "tried": 19
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "alla lavagna",
                "Alla lavagna"
            ],
            "answer": "Alla lavagna.",
            "failed": 13,
            "lastAsked": 1517253782.4197874,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Go to the board.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 20
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Cosa vuol dire",
                "cosa vuol dire",
                "cosa vuol dire?"
            ],
            "answer": "Cosa vuol dire?",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1517253776.8998358,
            "question": "Given the definition \"What does it mean?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 17
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "rispondate",
                "rispondete"
            ],
            "answer": "Rispondete.",
            "failed": 12,
            "lastAsked": 1517630293.3133657,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Answer.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 19
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ripete per favore",
                "ripeta per favore",
                "ripeta, per favore"
            ],
            "answer": "Ripeta, per favore!",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1517253771.5477626,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Repeat, please!\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 18
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vorrei andare ",
                "vorrei andare a"
            ],
            "answer": "vorrei andare a...",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1517253790.9236019,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I would like to go to...\"?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "quanto costa"
            ],
            "answer": "quanto costa?",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1517253818.5352628,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"How much does it cost?\"?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "come si scrive"
            ],
            "answer": "Come si scrive...?",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1517253856.7593443,
            "question": "Given the definition \"How do you spell...?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Do you have any"
            ],
            "answer": "Do you have?",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1517257150.998903,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ha?...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dov'e sono i negozi"
            ],
            "answer": "dove sono i negozi?",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1517253846.5630562,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where are the shops?\"?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vorrei vedere"
            ],
            "answer": "vorrei vedere...",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1517257114.295018,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I would like to see...\"?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ascoltate"
            ],
            "answer": "Ascoltate.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1517257132.41827,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Listen.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "voglio"
            ],
            "answer": "voglio...",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1517257159.1981964,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I want...\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dov'e c'e"
            ],
            "answer": "dove c'e'...",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516731407.9187012,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is there...\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "capite?",
                "Capite"
            ],
            "answer": "Capite?",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1516731385.0187774,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Do you understand?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "come stai?",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731603.089626,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"How are you?\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ripetete"
            ],
            "answer": "Ripetete.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731477.6015463,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Repeat.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "non mi piace"
            ],
            "answer": "non mi piace...",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731392.534324,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I don't like it...\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dov'e il bagno"
            ],
            "answer": "dov'e\" il bagno?",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731482.2822254,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is the bathroom?\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chiudete il libro"
            ],
            "answer": "Chiudete il libro.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731486.2822053,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Close the book.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "come?"
            ],
            "answer": "Come?",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731605.241114,
            "question": "Given the definition \"What?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "non capisco"
            ],
            "answer": "Non capisco.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517257142.446244,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I don't understand.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Dov'e sono i gabinetti",
                "dov'e sono i gabinetti",
                "dov'e sono i gabinetti?"
            ],
            "answer": "dove sono i gabinetti?",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517257129.0108373,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where are the toilets?\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "What does it mean?",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731548.129139,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Cosa vuol dire?\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here",
                "here is/are, there is/are"
            ],
            "answer": "Here is/are..., There is/are...",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731491.0659466,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ecco...\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vorrei compare"
            ],
            "answer": "vorrei compare...",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731650.0576997,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I would like to buy...\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "scrivete"
            ],
            "answer": "Scrivete.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731522.6700957,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Write.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "capisco"
            ],
            "answer": "Capisco.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731655.3296323,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I understand.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I want"
            ],
            "answer": "I want...",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1516731543.081245,
            "question": "Given the definition \"voglio...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I would like to see"
            ],
            "answer": "I would like to see...",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731598.065324,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vorrei vedere...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ha?",
                "Ha?"
            ],
            "answer": "Ha?...",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731539.145302,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Do you have?\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vorrei"
            ],
            "answer": "vorrei...",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731555.902061,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I would like...\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ecco"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco...",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731622.1570008,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Here is/are..., There is/are...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "come si pronuncia",
                "come si pronuncia?"
            ],
            "answer": "Come si pronuncia...?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731566.5573251,
            "question": "Given the definition \"How do you pronounce...?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am"
            ],
            "answer": "I am...",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731620.2368464,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sono...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "how do you spell"
            ],
            "answer": "How do you spell...?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731643.8650725,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Come si scrive...?\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "listen"
            ],
            "answer": "Listen.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731630.2124486,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ascoltate.\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a posto"
            ],
            "answer": "A posto.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1516731609.0569322,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Go back to your seat.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e tu?"
            ],
            "answer": "e lei?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731627.5016437,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And you?\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I would like to buy"
            ],
            "answer": "I would like to buy...",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731663.4174118,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vorrei compare...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I would like to go to",
                "I would like to go"
            ],
            "answer": "I would like to go to...",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731678.5395293,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vorrei andare a...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "mi piace"
            ],
            "answer": "mi piace...",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731681.9165003,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I like it...\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "mi chiamo"
            ],
            "answer": "mi chiamo...",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731749.588151,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My name is...\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "come si dice"
            ],
            "answer": "Come si dice...?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731675.0210392,
            "question": "Given the definition \"How do you say...?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "scusi"
            ],
            "answer": "scusi.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731746.884207,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am sorry.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "do you understand"
            ],
            "answer": "Do you understand?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1516731659.664543,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Capite?\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close the book"
            ],
            "answer": "Close the book.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731666.8046005,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Chiudete il libro.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "how do you say"
            ],
            "answer": "How do you say...?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731669.8444054,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Come si dice...?\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "what?"
            ],
            "answer": "What?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731671.7327828,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Come?\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "where is",
                "where is the"
            ],
            "answer": "Where is there...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731726.9645016,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dove c'e'...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I would like"
            ],
            "answer": "I would like...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731744.668594,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vorrei...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'm sorry",
                "I am sorry, excuse me",
                "I am sorry"
            ],
            "answer": "I am sorry.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731741.684549,
            "question": "Given the definition \"scusi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I understand"
            ],
            "answer": "I understand.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731685.5245187,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Capisco.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "go to your seat",
                "go back to your seat"
            ],
            "answer": "Go back to your seat.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731732.2523234,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"A posto.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "io sono",
                "sono"
            ],
            "answer": "sono...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731737.7969992,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am...\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "How are you (formal)",
                "how are you (formal)"
            ],
            "answer": "How are you? (polite)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1516731789.915556,
            "question": "Given the definition \"come sta?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "open the book"
            ],
            "answer": "Open the book.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731773.3605444,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Apirte il libro.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "where is the bathroom"
            ],
            "answer": "Where is the bathroom?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731777.8170564,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dov'e\" il bagno?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I don't want"
            ],
            "answer": "I don't want...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731806.752083,
            "question": "Given the definition \"non voglio...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dov'e c'e"
            ],
            "answer": "dov'e'...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731831.913083,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is...\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "where"
            ],
            "answer": "Where is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731792.356054,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dov'e'...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "go to the board"
            ],
            "answer": "Go to the board.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731803.080062,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Alla lavagna.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I do not like",
                "I don't like it"
            ],
            "answer": "I don't like it...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731766.1441891,
            "question": "Given the definition \"non mi piace...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "My name",
                "I am called"
            ],
            "answer": "My name is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731852.468241,
            "question": "Given the definition \"mi chiamo...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "where are the shops"
            ],
            "answer": "Where are the shops?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731827.1361098,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dove sono i negozi?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "How do you pronounce",
                "how do you pronounce"
            ],
            "answer": "How do you pronounce...?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731861.6725771,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Come si pronuncia...?\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "answer"
            ],
            "answer": "Answer.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731855.3880954,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Rispondete.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "and you (formal)",
                "and you?"
            ],
            "answer": "And you?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731754.6923678,
            "question": "Given the definition \"e lei?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "where are the toilets?"
            ],
            "answer": "Where are the toilets?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731842.9482746,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dove sono i gabinetti?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "please repeat",
                "repeat please"
            ],
            "answer": "Repeat, please!",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731866.3600333,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ripeta, per favore!\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I like"
            ],
            "answer": "I like it...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731794.3807719,
            "question": "Given the definition \"mi piace...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "come sta?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731769.5121694,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"How are you? (polite)\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e tu / e lei?"
            ],
            "answer": "e tu?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731818.135932,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"And you? (2)\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'm sorry",
                "I am sorry"
            ],
            "answer": "Excuse me...?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731811.5600555,
            "question": "Given the definition \"scusi...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I don't understand"
            ],
            "answer": "I don't understand.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731836.3164544,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Non capisco.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "write",
                "to write"
            ],
            "answer": "Write.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731759.953269,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Scrivete.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "repeat"
            ],
            "answer": "Repeat.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731847.2036438,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ripetete.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "how are you (informal)"
            ],
            "answer": "How are you?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731823.144194,
            "question": "Given the definition \"come stai?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "scusi"
            ],
            "answer": "scusi...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731779.7723262,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Excuse me...?\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "and you?"
            ],
            "answer": "And you? (2)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731845.2272985,
            "question": "Given the definition \"e tu?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "how much does it cost"
            ],
            "answer": "How much does it cost?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1516731797.764113,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quanto costa?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        }
    ]
}